I can see you .
... went into this gas station , the guy was like ,
" Yo , man , you got problems . "
Like , " What the hell do you think I pulled in here for ? "
So your car broke down on the way to your blood check .
Yeah , smoke , everything .
I 'm willing to give you the benefit of the doubt , Javier , but a judge won 't .
I missed a couple of meetings ?
What 's the problem ?
I mean , I don 't even know what I 'm doing here .
You 're here because your son has gotten into fights every day at school ,
and the last one sent one of his classmates to the hospital .
Juanita came here for help voluntarily
before the court stepped in and made it mandatory ,
that 's what you 're doing here .
He 's on a dangerous road .
Your history , all the violence , all the anger ,
that 's his future unless you break the cycle .
I heard you , Mrs Lynch .
You 're trying to steal my boy !
No one is trying to steal your child .
- Then what are you trying ... - They found bruises
- and cigarette burns ... - I told you ,
he was playing with some sparklers .
Mrs Lynch , I read the medical report .
I wanna talk to my own doctor .
I want a lawyer .
If you feel that you need legal representation
that 's perfectly within your rights ...
I don 't need your help , in no case .
You 've already interfered enough .
You ... Hello ?
- How many active cases you got ? - Thirty-eight .
- Okay . - Wayne , come on !
Look , I 'm buried here .
I 'm sorry , Em , we all are .
- You have three new voice messages . - Hi .
Hey , it 's Suze , missed you at yoga the other day , give me a call .
Hey , Em , it 's Jackie .
Just checking in , hope you 're good .
Exhausted , her career path questionable ,
her faith in mankind shaken ,
she resisted her tendency toward introspection
and decides to go have a drink with her charming friend Doug .
- I am so in your head . - Be honest .
The whole psychology thing , it 's just about scoring chicks , isn 't it ?
Regrettably , yes . Two .
Well , what are we gonna drink to tonight ?
The never-ending fun of a career in public service ?
Yeah .
You know , I sit there talking to these families ,
the authority on everything .
And I have these moments where I think I might be totally full of it .
Everybody 's full of it .
In the end you 're a number to call for people who don 't have anyone else .
There 's no way that 's bad .
Anyway , I 've done some soul searching
and I just want to say
that if a full-on relationship feels like too much right now ,
I 'd be willing to consider a purely physical one .
- What ? - Nothing .
What , you might actually enjoy yourself .
Yeah , yeah , I probably would .
- It 's just ... - I know , I know , the job ,
you get home , no time for anybody else . Whatever .
Listen , I 'm giving you a month . Okay ? One month .
- And then ? - I don 't know .
Probably give you another month , but that is it .
Except for two more , then , it 's over .
If it were anyone ...
What are they doing to you ?
- What ? - Emily Jenkins . Child Services ?
We spoke on the phone ?
- You said the 17th . - It 's the 17th .
- Is not . - I 'm sorry , but it is .
Monday the 17th .
The day of our appointment .
Hi .
Come down , I 'd like to meet you .
My name 's Emily .
What 's yours ?
- Lily . - That 's a pretty name .
Is there somewhere we can talk ?
So , when are you expecting your husband back ?
Because we 've found that it 's better when the whole family participates .
Well , he 's not here , so ...
Do you have some way of contacting him ?
Not if I don 't know where he is .
Is that ...
Would you mind asking him to join us , please ?
He doesn 't have anything to say .
Will you ask him , please ?
Edward .
That lady is here from the state .
She wants to talk to you .
I don 't have anything to say , tell her that !
I told her already , she wants to anyway .
It 'll be okay .
Hi , I 'm Emily .
Okay .
I 'm here because we received a call
that Lilith is showing serious signs of neglect .
Now at this point we can only assume it 's the result of family problems .
Eddie says we don 't have family problems .
Well , many families won 't realise that they 're having problems
until it 's too late .
And that 's where we come in .
We help families communicate
and learn healthier ways of resolving conflict .
Eddie says we don 't need your help .
Mr Sullivan , is there a reason why you won 't speak to me directly ?
Is there a reason why your husband won 't speak to me directly ?
Eddie doesn 't like speaking out of anger .
There 's no laws against being weird , Em .
I didn 't say weird , I said scary .
That man sat there staring at me the whole time ,
and the mother is his emotional slave .
Wait , you didn 't just fly to New York and meet with my parents , did you ?
Wayne ?
All right . All right .
Are there any cuts , any bruises ,
any signs she 's being abused ?
No , not physically .
But this girl 's in trouble , I can feel it .
You wanna know what I can feel ?
The lawsuit we 're gonna get hit with if we violate her parents ' rights
without any evidence they 've done something wrong .
All right , Wayne .
You put these files on my desk
and you ask me to tell you what 's going on .
I 've told you , I 've done my job , what you do with it is yours .
We 're not perfect parents , we know that ,
but we figure if they know how much you love them
a lot of the other stuff takes care of itself .
She knows how we feel about her .
So , tell me , Mr Sullivan ,
since you 've suddenly acquired the ability to speak ,
doesn 't it concern you a little
that Lily 's grades have dropped from A 's to D 's in three months ?
Of course it does , she 's our daughter .
So you have no idea why your daughter falls asleep in class every day ?
Why she can 't sleep at home ? No idea ?
Bad dreams maybe ?
Don 't tell me you 're buying this whole " daddy 's little girl " routine ?
Look , they 're not my favourite people either , okay ?
But we can 't guarantee every kid a happy childhood .
I wish we could .
Let me talk to her .
She wants to talk . Alone .
Em , we do not have a case .
Just five minutes , okay ?
Talk to them about how much they love kids .
Hey , girls , slow down !
I used to wish I had a sister when I was growing up .
To play with and to talk to
about all those things that you just can 't tell anybody else , you know ?
Did you ever wish that ?
That you had a sister ?
Well , that was a silly thing to do , wasn 't it ?
What 's happening with you ?
You know I can help .
Let me help you .
What is it , sweetheart ?
They hate me .
I 'm sure they don 't hate you .
They do . I hear them .
They go into the cellar and talk .
What do they talk about ?
Sending me to hell .
You heard them say that ?
You can tell him .
He 's on your side .
It 's okay .
Lily , did you hear your parents say they were gonna hurt you ?
I was just thinking about you , got a nice letter from Sandy Hutchinson .
Well , well , well .
It 's sitting right in front of me , which means our good friend Wayne
has decided it fails to meet the criteria for child endangerment
and has told you in no uncertain terms to leave it alone .
Surprise , surprise .
I 'm sorry , Emily . I can 't .
Please , Mike , I 'm really desperate here .
Emily .
Now , you know how dear to my heart the work you do is ,
but the department doesn 't pay me to stake out potential child abusers .
Last time almost cost me my job .
This little girl heard her parents say they 're going to send her to hell .
Sickening as that is ,
you 're a part of the system that deals with those situations , I 'm not .
But sometimes the system doesn 't work .
Well , maybe you should just let it .
Wow . Feel like I 'm talking to Wayne here .
All right . You don 't want to get involved , that 's fine ,
but don 't bullshit me , Mike , I 'm running out of people I respect .
Okay . No bullshit .
Bring me evidence of a crime , I 'm all over it . Till then ...
Let 's go , hurry up !
Lily ! Lily !
Hi . I came to tell you I hadn 't forgotten about you .
I 'm doing everything I can .
If I disappear will you come look for me ?
- You 're not going to disappear . - If I do ?
I have to go .
They get mad at me when I miss the bus .
Lily , wait . Wait .
Here . It 's my home number .
If you get scared , I want you to call me , okay ?
I 'm gonna get you out of there , I promise .
Okay .
Hey , this is Doug , here it comes .
Hey , it 's me , thought you might be awake .
Just calling ' cause ...
Well , I don 't really know why I 'm calling .
Call me if you get this , okay ?
... proposal in Morton Township has some residents ...
Here we go golfers and shoppers ...
Let 's look at the crepe batter .
In order to make the crepe batter ...
- Too late , I met someone else . - Emily .
Lily ? Are you okay ?
- I 'm scared . - Why , honey ? Why are you scared ?
They 're waiting to get me , I can hear them .
- I 'm sorry . - Why are you sorry ?
- I 'm falling asleep . - Okay , listen .
Go over and open the window .
Can you do that ?
- I 'm sorry . - Lily ? Lily ?
- Yeah , Barron . - Mike , it 's Emily .
That girl that I told you about , I think she 's in a lot of trouble .
Emily , you 're going ...
No , I know what you said .
Mike , you 're not listening ! Help me !
What are we doing here , Emily ?
Saving her life !
They 're asleep like we should be .
They 're not asleep .
Did you hear that ?
I didn 't hear anything .
Leave her alone !
No !
Let me out !
Did you hear that ?
Police , open up !
Stop !
Break , break it down .
Break it down !
Help me . Help me .
- Police ! - Lily !
Lily !
God ! Oh , my God !
No ! Help me !
Please , help me .
I got you , I got you , I got ...
Okay . I got you .
What the hell 's the matter with you people ?
I got you .
It 's okay , honey .
It 's okay . I got you .
The egregiousness of the crime makes
the competency question all the more relevant .
I hereby order the defendants to undergo psychiatric evaluation
to determine their fitness for trial .
Steal a pizza , San Quentin .
Try to kill your kid , Freudian dream analysis .
You 're gonna hate me for saying this but my money 's on crazy .
What kind of people put their kid in an oven ?
Bad people . Remember that when people were just bad ?
Before everything had a diagnosis and a justification ?
It 's human nature .
What 's the most important thing
that we talked about that you have to remember ?
It 's not my fault what happened .
That 's right . You know what ? It 's not .
Good . I 'll see you soon .
- Hey . - Hi .
That is some seriously proactive social work happening there .
- You all right ? - Yeah , I 'm fine .
How 's she doing ?
Typical reaction .
But she blames herself .
We 'll get there .
I 'm gonna put her in a group setting , see if I can get her to open up .
Group therapy for kids , when am I going to get used to that ?
- See you later . Okay . - See you .
Hi .
Good news .
They say you can get out of here tomorrow .
Doug said I might have to go to a state home .
Yeah , but it 's only temporary , till we find you a nice family .
Why can 't I live with you ?
Sweetheart , that would never be allowed .
Why ?
Well , it 's complicated , I mean , there 's this whole process ,
and I 'm not even a foster parent . So ...
It 'll be fine .
- Hi , Barb . - Hi , Em . Right this way , little lady .
I 'll check in , in a couple of days , okay ?
I don 't want to stay here , I want to live with you .
Please . I 'll be good .
Lily , it 's impossible , I told you .
Will you try ?
Honey , listen , even if they said yes , it would never work .
I work all day and I 'm hardly ever home and ...
I 'm sorry , I 'm just not mom material .
How do you know if you 've never tried ?
So , it 's just until we can find the right family for her ,
just until we can place her in a really good home .
You know you 'd have to give up the case , conflict of interests and all .
Yeah .
Can I ask you a question ?
Why are you doing this ?
What Lily needs right now is a safe , supportive environment
with someone she trusts .
The system can 't provide that for her , I think that I can .
Better than anyone , given my training .
We spend so much of our time negotiating red tape ,
I think if we look at this situation , this one situation ,
this one child , it 's clear what 's best for her .
How long till Foster Services can place her in a permanent home ?
Three weeks , three months , it 's hard to predict .
No more visits .
- What ? - They said yes .
It 's your new beginning .
Okay . It 's what I like to think of as a glass-half-full situation .
Bathroom . Kitchen . Fish .
And this is your room .
Be okay ?
- You live alone ? - Just me .
Just us .
What 's this ?
It 's chamomile .
Helps me sleep .
You know none of this should ever have happened .
If I could make it go away , I would .
You did .
Here . Climb in .
Night night .
ï ¿ ½ P @ rM ! NdeR M @ nkï ¿ ½ï ¿ ½ ï ¿ ½
- Okay . All right . - Here we go .
- Just got to grab some of her things . - Okay .
So , here 's the key .
You 're not coming ?
I got 15 other places I got to be .
So make sure you lock it on the way out . Okay ? Bye .
The kids at school are saying all this stuff like saying
my mother is a puta
and I mean , I know we can 't go back home
but I miss it .
Sometimes when our parents aren 't getting along ,
it 's better if they spend some time apart .
That 's what a restraining order does .
She 's starting to come out of her shell .
It 's good , but you got to expect some hiccups .
And you can 't undo 10 years of trauma in six weeks .
School ? Too soon ?
No , I don 't have a problem with her going back ,
just as long as she 's comfortable with it .
I went by the house .
I think her mom and dad were
barricading themselves in their room at night .
How sick is that ?
Well , fear and hatred are part of the same pathology .
- See you . Bye , Diego . - You too , Lily .
- But I forgot . - Bye .
- Bye . - You don 't think they 're crazy .
Well , I 'm coming around .
- I love you . - Love you , too .
- Wayne 's looking for you . - Okay .
Wayne wants to see you .
Yeah , I got it .
What 's up with Diego ?
Oh , hey .
Look , why don 't we go talk in my office .
No , tell me what 's going on .
Well , we don 't ...
.. We don 't know why yet but he killed both his parents last night .
Excuse me ... Go ahead .
Officer , let her through .
What happened ?
Gets a tyre iron from the garage , comes back inside ,
locks all the doors and windows , and kills them in their sleep .
" Slaughters " would be a better word .
Oh , my God !
A 10-year-old did this ? There 's no way .
I was there when they brought him in .
Took three guys to subdue him .
And the kid was climbing the walls .
Man 's best friend , huh ?
What happened ?
Tell me what happened .
I killed my mom and dad .
Every family you sit down with ,
every day of every week , it 's a family in crisis .
Those are your odds .
Well , that 's your job , trying to beat them .
You 're one person , Em .
You can 't save the world .
I know somebody you did save .
Yeah .
- You okay ? - Yeah .
It 's just work . Don 't worry .
- I think you have a hard job . - So do I.
People have kids and then they decide they don 't want to be parents .
And then the kids grow up thinking it 's their fault .
Is that what your parents did ?
You said you were alone .
Yeah .
I never met my dad .
And my mom ... My mom had problems .
She must have scared you .
Why do you say that ?
You don 't like to talk about it .
You 're a clever little girl .
Sweetheart .
Breakfast .
What you got ?
Let me see .
You went through my things ?
I 'm sorry .
I wanted to know about you .
Is that your mother ?
What happened to her ?
She died when I was about your age .
- How ? - An accident .
It was raining and she was driving too fast .
We had an accident .
Are you mad at me ?
No , I 'm not mad at you .
But I need you not to do that again , okay ?
Go through my private things without asking .
Okay ? All right .
Omelette 's getting cold .
Better hurry .
You watch , six months , their lawyer will hire an expert
to say they 're rehabbed and they 'll sue for custody when they get out .
She 's not going back there .
I 'll take her out of the state before I let them near her again .
Didn 't hear you say that .
You guys okay ?
We 're great . She 's sweet , very intuitive about everything .
You wanted to talk about something ?
We pulled the Ramirezes ' phone records .
There was a call that night before the murder .
From who ?
The call came from your house , Emily .
What ?
I 'm not accusing you of anything , I just want to know what was said .
But that 's impossible .
I mean , I might have called them the week before or something , but I ...
I 'm talking to you as a friend , you know that , right ?
Mike , did you not hear me ?
As a friend , I 'm telling you that I didn 't call that family .
He 's in my group .
Why , did something happen ?
We 're trying to figure out why .
Diego got a call from here , last Thursday night .
I 'm just wondering if he might have said something .
That wasn 't me .
You didn 't call him ?
Lily , it 's difficult sometimes to tell the truth ,
but I know you will because you 're a good kid .
I am telling the truth .
My backup files are in the cabinet .
Diego 's is in there .
Maybe you got curious and went through some , dialled a number ?
It wasn 't me , I swear .
The call came at 2 : 00 a.m.
You ever up that late ?
I didn 't call him .
Mike , she said no .
Maybe somebody made a mistake .
Yeah , maybe so .
Why would Diego do this ?
He loved his mom and dad .
You never want to think anyone you know is capable of that kind of thing .
In your mind , it 's always some nameless , faceless creature .
Sometimes , the city seems full of them .
But they 're just people , like you and me .
She 's lying .
Do you believe me ?
I believe you .
I need to ask you something about the night it happened .
Did you get a call ?
Really late ?
You didn 't .
Diego , I know that you did .
The call came from my house .
What 's the matter ?
What 's scaring you ? Diego .
It 's okay , it 's all right .
Deep breaths , deep breaths , you 'll be all right .
Can we get some help in here , please ?
Who called you ?
Was it Lily ?
Did she say something to you ?
Something that scared you ?
- ï ¿ ½l dijo . - " ï ¿ ½l dijo " ?
What do you mean , " He said " ?
Era un hombre .
It was a man ?
Do you
like working here ?
Well , photocopying isn 't much fun .
- What ? - Knock , knock . Sorry I 'm late , guys .
You ready to go , kiddo ?
- So , how 's school ? - Fine .
Any of your classmates giving you a hard time ?
No , they 've been nice .
You sleeping okay ?
That 's not really what you want to talk about , is it , Doug ?
You got me .
Question 16 , am I afraid of the dark ?
You answered no .
Question 23 , am I afraid of being alone ?
26 , am I afraid of my parents ? No .
You answered no to everything in that section .
I think that some of those should have been yeses .
Everybody is scared of something .
Working through our fears , conquering them ,
is how we get better .
So , I want you to tell me , what scares you ?
I 'll tell you what scares me if you tell me what scares you .
Fair enough .
When I was a kid , I was climbing a tree ,
and I accidentally put my hand through a giant hornets ' nest .
And they didn 't like it .
I was stung over a hundred times .
They had to rush me to the hospital .
Been afraid of hornets ever since .
I don 't climb many trees either .
Everybody has fears .
Now , what scares you ?
- Me . - You scare yourself ?
Sometimes .
Why ? What about yourself scares you ?
I have bad thoughts .
- About what ? - People .
People in general or certain people ?
Certain people .
- Like who ? - You .
You have bad thoughts about me ?
- Why ? - I just do .
Did I do something or say something that upset you ?
It 's just the way you are .
How am I ?
- Facile . - Facile ?
Do you even know what that means ?
Easily comprehended .
Often lacking sincerity or depth .
You 're smug , too .
Want me to tell you what that means ?
If I seemed smug or facile I want to ...
Don 't apologise .
Why not ?
You 're a grown-up .
It 's embarrassing .
Number 12 , I worry about
what 's going to happen .
Yes or no ?
You want me to answer that ?
- Yes or no ? - No .
That should be a yes .
Should we talk about school now ?
My grades are getting a lot better .
I talked to a lot of kids , I don 't think I 've ever felt like that before .
Like what ?
Threatened .
I know a specialist , I 'm gonna call him in the morning .
Are you mad at me ?
No . No , I 'm just tired .
Want me to brush your hair ?
No , thanks .
Are you sure ?
Some other time .
It will make you feel better .
I 'll get the brush .
I said no , thank you .
Doug said something , didn 't he ?
Doug ? No .
Doug says you 're doing great .
- What did he tell you ? - Nothing .
Hello .
Try again , sorry .
For as much as it hath pleased Almighty God ,
of his great mercy , to take unto himself the soul
of our dear brother , here departed ,
we , therefore , commit his body to the ground .
Earth to earth , ashes to ashes and dust to dust ,
in sure and certain hope of the resurrection to eternal life ,
through our Lord , Jesus Christ , amen .
You think it 's my fault , don 't you ?
It 's no one 's fault .
It was an accident .
There was no sign of forced entry ,
he was alone and the doors were locked .
I know he didn 't kill himself .
He was scared .
He came out of that room with her , Mike , and he was scared .
He said she threatened him .
Emily , you 're in shock , let 's not get carried away .
Diego , he said it was a man on the phone .
There was no one else in the house .
Do you think I don 't know how crazy this sounds ?
Kid in that state of mind is not the most reliable witness .
But why was he in that state of mind ?
Why was Doug ?
Pull my phone records .
See if she called him .
I already did , Emily .
There was no call .
So , you 're saying that you 've seen this before ,
someone just dying like that ?
Truly ? I 'm shocked every day by the violence people do to themselves .
Her mom and dad had deadbolts on their bedroom door , big ones .
Something came through that door , and whatever it was ,
they didn 't want it ever coming through there again .
Hey guys , come on , are you ready ?
Yeah .
- Let 's get to it ? - Yeah .
Take me through the conversation , Margaret , about the oven .
Eddie said , " We 're gonna burn her , " and I said , " Okay . "
So it was Edward 's idea ?
Just the oven part , we both wanted her dead .
Why did you say that it was God 's will that you should kill your daughter ?
Why is that funny , Margaret ?
' Cause she 's not my daughter .
You think your daughter is the devil ?
Evil incarnate ?
I don 't care what you call it .
But you have stated that she kills people ?
Not by her own hand , they just die .
I had two brothers ,
Eddie had three sisters .
Soon as she was born , they just started dying .
Me and Eddie , I guess ,
she couldn 't get rid of us until she found somebody else .
ï ¿ ½
ï ¿ ½ P @ rM ! NdeR
ï ¿ ½ P @ rM ! NdeR M @ nkï ¿ ½
ï ¿ ½ P @ rM ! NdeR M @ nkï ¿ ½ï ¿ ½
ï ¿ ½ P @ rM ! NdeR M @ nkï ¿ ½ï ¿ ½ ï ¿ ½
The nurse on duty heard screaming ,
found Mrs Sullivan on the floor clawing at her own skin ,
absolutely convinced she was on fire .
In no condition for visitors as you can see .
If you 'd like , I can let you see Mr Sullivan .
Okay .
I know I 'm probably the last person you want to see right now ,
but you 're the only one that I can talk to .
Who died ?
- A friend . - You 're scared .
You ought to be .
Is she ...
What is she ?
I can tell you what she 's not .
She 's not a daughter of mine .
She 's not a 10-year-old having trouble in school .
And she 's not some innocent victim whose door you busted down
and life you saved .
She 's not going anywhere soon , lady .
Not till she 's good and done with you .
Done with me how ?
However she wants .
You think it 's an accident her ending up with you ?
She saw you coming a mile away .
Why me ? I don 't have anything .
You have that you 're good . Kindness .
Decency . That 's what she feeds on .
Bleeds you dry , moves on to the next .
We were a big family ,
she went through us like a wrecking ball .
It 's like she sees everything .
And what she doesn 't see , she senses .
Like when you call a friend and they pick it up before it rings ?
They say when you 're born you 're given your eternal soul .
The part of you that lives on , lives again .
Whatever evil she is , didn 't come from us .
It was already there .
From the moment she came into being , she brought something with her .
Something older , destructive .
Soul of a demon .
What does she want ?
To know what your idea of hell is
and make you live there .
- Hi . - Hi .
You weren 't there so I took the bus .
Sorry , work , I lost track of time .
It 's okay , I know how busy you are .
Doesn 't matter anyway , the bus stops right at the end of the street .
So I can always get home , whether you 're there or not .
Lucky .
Where 's the phone ?
It wasn 't working , so ...
Wow . That one , too .
We had gym today .
I 'm gonna have a shower .
- Are they being nice to her ? - Who ?
My mother .
How would I know that ?
I thought you said you were going to see her .
I never said that .
I must have dreamt it .
- Nancy . - Emily .
I 'm so sorry about Doug .
I know you two were close .
Do you have a minute ?
I was just wondering if you 've had any luck finding a place for Lilith ?
Still looking .
You know , more kids than homes right now .
So , how long you think we 're talking here ? Like ...
Honestly , she 's not my first priority .
She 's in a safe environment with someone who understands her needs .
Nancy ,
if there 's anything that you could do to expedite
- the process ... - Are you serious ?
Emily , you petitioned for custody , you got it .
She 's your responsibility . Make it work .
How ?
How do I make it work if it 's not working ?
With the same coping skills you teach these moms and dads every week !
Walk the talk , Emily ! Walk the talk !
See you next time . Good work .
Why is she hurting ...
Hey , wait a minute .
Who do you think you are , barging in there like that ?
It 's okay , Diane , Emily 's been under a lot of stress lately ,
but she 's really nice to me and I hope I can stay with her a long time .
Don 't ever do that again .
See you next week , Diane .
Don 't worry , it was all a misunderstanding .
- You 're not going back there . - Why , Emily ?
Why , Emily ? Why , Emily ? Why , Emily ?
Why , Emily ? Why , Emily ?
Why , Emily ?
Can I go back to group next week ?
You 're never going back there !
Are you sure ?
No . No .
- I know . - You were terrific back there .
Really enjoyed the service , Father . Thanks .
- Mike . - Emily .
They are not crazy , Mike . Her parents .
They 're right about her .
You want to wind up where they are ?
Keep talking like this .
Emily , you 're grieving for Doug
and you 're still confused about what Diego did .
Aren 't you ?
Diego grew up in a bad home ,
he saw violence , he repeated it , that 's the cycle .
You know that better than anyone .
Why did she lie about calling him ?
Because she 's a liar , but that doesn 't mean she made him do it .
Let me tell you what Lily is .
She 's a damaged child , she 's a deceitful child ,
she 's a manipulative child .
But a damaged , deceitful , manipulative child is not a demon .
You think I 'm crazy .
You believe in there .
But out here it 's all just bullshit ?
Mike , you know I 'm not crazy .
Don 't run away from this just because it scares you .
I 'll tell you what is scaring me is not recognising my friend .
- Get some help . Seriously . - Mike ...
I don 't want to report you .
Good night .
Mrs Lynch , I told you that ...
Do you think I 'm an idiot ?
Do you think I 'm just making this up ?
- That 's not what you said .
I 'm not stupid . Yeah , no .
You never said anything about unsupervised visits .
No , that is not what I said .
You said if my husband got help , then my son could come home .
I did not . No .
Nothing between the lines there .
You never said that ...
Who do you think you are telling me how to raise my son ?
- Mrs Lynch ... - You know nothing about me .
You know nothing about my son .
You know nothing about my family .
Will you please let me respond ?
How I raise my child is none of your business .
Would you let ... Would you ...
How my son and his father relate is none of your business .
Shut the fuck up , you miserable , miserable woman
before I come and beat your ass like you beat your son !
I have your address !
Think about that before you call and swear at me !
Okay , so , you 're certainly in no state of mind to be here right now .
Come on , it 's late , you look like shit , go home .
I don 't want to go home .
Hello ?
It 's for you .
Emily Jenkins .
You shouldn 't leave me home alone , Emily .
Wayne ?
There you are .
I made supper .
Don 't ignore me .
My mother used to ignore me .
Emily ? Can I come in ?
I 'm scared .
Emily ? Please ?
I know you 're in there .
Please , Emily ?
Let me in , let me in .
Let me in , let me in , let me in , let me in ,
let me in , let me in , let me in .
Leave me alone .
Please , help me .
Please ! No , please open the door ?
Open the door , she 's coming !
- Drive . - There 's nobody out there .
Drive !
There is nobody out there . Look .
There 's nobody out there .
It 's okay .
Leaving the child unattended is a jailable offence .
You have to do what I say .
If I say I want to go to group , you have to do it .
If I say I want a new dress , you have to do it .
If I say I want ice cream every day , after school ,
you have to do it , okay ?
Don 't be sad .
This is your new beginning .
Emily .
I tried to call you .
Good news , we found a home for Lily .
Family in Cloverfield .
Really good people .
They 're picking her up Friday , after school .
What 's the matter ?
They 're perfect .
If they take her ...
The whole thing starts all over again .
You can 't let her go , you can 't let her stay .
Leaves you one option .
- I can 't . - You have to .
You don 't understand .
Don 't tell me I don 't understand .
You 've had her , what , two months ?
I had her 10 years .
We had her 10 years .
Think of it as a test of faith .
I don 't wanna have any faith .
How about anger ?
You got some of that ?
How ? How do I ...
Kill her ?
In her asleep .
That 's the only time you got the upper hand , is when she 's sleeping ,
but she almost never does .
We checked on her room , every night for three months .
First night she slept was the night that you busted in our front door .
And I 'll tell you what I 'd do different , count yourself dead at the outset .
Accept that going in , use it to your advantage .
If you 're not afraid , she can 't hurt you .
No money , no way to contact her .
Must have went 80 on the way back , straight through ,
didn 't stop for nothing .
When we got home , she was waiting for us on the doorstep .
Where is she now ?
Some family , somewhere ?
Eddie said , " We 're gonna burn her , " and I said , " Okay . "
They did what I said for a while , but then they stopped
and started with the secrets .
But they weren 't really secrets , I guess ,
because I always knew what they were thinking .
Don 't leave me .
It 's okay , Maggie .
I 'll check on you later .
I 'm glad you 're getting the help you need , Daddy .
Get somebody down here now .
Somebody call it in .
Base , this is Sanchez .
We 're gonna need medical personnel right away to the cafeteria ...
- Edward Sullivan ... - I know .
Something I want you to hear .
This came in this morning , right about 2 : 00 a.m.
You might wanna sit .
... decide what to do with you and your family , Michael .
Every time I think about it , a voice in my head says , " Kill them . "
Who is this ?
Just a little girl .
Up past her bedtime .
Lilith ?
You were right . She did call Doug .
She used your cell phone .
Took me a couple of extra days to check your cell phone records ,
but that 's what she 's been using .
She 's tearing me apart .
You 're not crazy , Emily . This is real .
Edward said I have to kill her .
I 'll help you .
Keep her at the house .
Physically you 're fine .
How 's the stress ?
I 'm not sleeping .
I was hoping you could give me something .
Take one of these , you 'll sleep .
Lily ?
What ?
Oh , my God .
Who is this ?
Emily , it 's Wayne ,
I just got a call , Mike 's dead .
- No , he 's ... - Listen , Em .
They think he shot himself .
- Emily ? Em ? - No ...
Emily ?
Emily , are you okay ?
ï ¿ ½ P @ rM ! NdeR M @ nkï ¿ ½ï ¿ ½ ï ¿ ½
Get out of my house !
Don 't yell at me !
Emily , I 'm sorry .
I didn 't mean to .
Can I come in so we can talk and work it out ?
Emily ?
Stay away from me !
Don 't be mad .
I said I was sorry .
I 'll brush your hair for you .
Stay away from me !
No ! No . No .
Emily . Emily .
We need to learn healthier ways of resolving conflict , Emily .
Most families don 't even know they have a problem
until it 's too late .
What are you doing , you silly pumpkinhead ?
You don 't want me to come under there and get you , do you ?
- No . - I 'm going to count to three .
One , two ...
No .
Two and a half , two and three quarters ,
three . Here I come .
No ! What do you want ?
What you wanted from your mother .
I want you to love me .
Okay . I will .
Come tuck me in .
Oh , my God .
Emily .
Chamomile .
Maybe you should have it , you look stressed .
I 'll have one later .
I 'm really sorry that I let things get like this .
We 'll do better from now on .
We have to .
Someone could get hurt .
What should we do tomorrow ?
Surprise me .
I 'm not so good at surprises .
You 're getting better .
Everybody get out okay ?
Ma 'am , anyone else inside ?
Yes or no ?
That was mean .
You follow us downtown , we 'll find someplace for you to stay .
Miss ? You okay ?
I 'm fine .
Maybe we can find a hotel with a swimming pool .
Where are we going ?
You said I should surprise you .
She hated herself .
And she hated you .
They said it was an accident , but you knew it wasn 't .
Your mother .
That 's why you never had any kids of your own .
That 's what you 're afraid of , isn 't it ?
The part of you that 's her .
What are you ?
Slow down !
What the hell are you ?
You 're upset , you shouldn 't be driving .
Mom .
Mom , slow down , you 're scaring me .
Mom ! Slow down , please !
Look out !
- It 's not real . - Yes , it is !
It 's not real !
Are you scared ?
I 'm not .
I 'm not afraid .
Just die !
No ! No !
Corrected and Synced by StarTrek6428